GOD IS STILL SAYING SOMETHING
On 26th July 2009, during a Sunday live service at The SCOAN,
Prophet T.B. Joshua gave a call to pray for the nation Iran.
These were his words.
In Jesus' name.
Pray for the nation Iran.
Please, open your lips and pray for the nation.
Prayer.
In Jesus' name we pray.
God's intervention.
On Sunday 6th November 2011,
Prophet T.B. Joshua gave another prophetic message about the nation Iran.
He called for peace between the nations, specifically Iran and Israel.
He then called on the congregation and viewers to pray for God's intervention.
We should pray for a nation to nation.
There was a prophecy I gave - pray for a country, Iran, and other super nations
that crisis---
I said it three years ago.
It is very close now.
I want everyone to be on their knees.
We don't want crisis again; we don't want war again.
We don't want an attack again.
Whatever God will do to put an end to crises from nation to nation---
I'm seeing crisis between these countries.
Be on your knees and pray.
Ask God - we need peace.
God's intervention.
It's close now - very, very close.
I'm seeing an attack. I'm seeing a fight between nation to nation.
Three years ago, I mentioned particularly Iran, that they should pray.
Pray for God's intervention.
God should settle every difference.
Ask God for intervention for that nation and other nations.
We don't want it.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Because the war is not going to bring solution to the whole world,
rather, crisis.
We want God's intervention.
God's intervention
In the whole world
We need God's intervention
God's intervention
In the whole world
We need God's intervention
Father, we thank You.
We want God's intervention in whatever differences between nation to nation.
We pray for the nation, Iran.
We pray for the nation, Israel.
God's intervention in whatever differences.
Father, with You, all things are possible.
We know, to Your power, everything is possible.
Father, we thank You.
Pray for God's intervention.
We know our God is able.
He is able
More than able
To accomplish what concerns
Me today
He is able
More than able
And He can handle
Anything that comes my way
He is able
More than able
To do much more
Than I could ever dream
He is able
More than able
To make me what He wants me to be
On Sunday, February 5th 2012, Prophet T.B. Joshua referred to the prophetic message
he had been speaking about for the past three years
concerning tension between the nations of Iran and Israel.
He then illustrated what would occur between the nations
if the tension continued and gave a call to pray for the whole world.
Last year, I reminded you of what I said three years ago
to pray for the nation Iran.
And I also said that I'm seeing tension between Iran and Israel.
I then said it last year, that what I was talking about was very close -
the tension of, I want to fight; you want to fight.
It's close; any moment from now, you will hear it.
And we all went on our knees.
Because if that should happen, it would be very serious,
more than any other one you have ever witnessed.
We went on our knees and we begged God.
But the prayer we offered that day, I know it will not go in vain.
Now, we'll follow the prayer.
They will continue to discuss, coming to a kind of compromise,
agreement and so on and so forth.
This will continue to drag until the full understanding comes.
But we should not stop praying because a break in prayer -
war will start.
Let us pray.
This one will be different from others.
This is why we don't want a fight.
If this kind of fight starts, every other one you have read about is an atom.
This one will be an element.
You know atom to element - how big the size is.
So that is it.
This one is not an issue of fighting a country to country
but the whole world should begin to pray that this should not happen;
they should come to an understanding and dialogue.
Because if this thing happens, many countries will join in support of others.
Trouble has come.
And it will not be an issue of---
Come on.
I'm talking to you; you are talking to me.
It's between me and you.
I will not agree! I will not!
God should stop the two of us.
If not---
Come.
You want to support this man to fight me.
You want to support me.
You want to support this man.
Come. You want to support this man.
You want to support me.
What is coming?
World War.
Sit down.
PROPHECY FOR ISRAEL AND IRAN | Prophet TB Joshua
So, I'm talking to you in parables.
This is the only way I can say it.
So, this is why I said, it's not like others.
The whole scenario, it's not like others.
So please, we should be very careful all over the world.
It's not like others.
Others may just go; but this one, it will spread.
So please, dialogue, settlement.
Thank you.
Rise up for this moment.
I want us to bow down our heads and pray to God for peace all over the world.
Pray that the world should be ready to shift ground.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Amen.
We pray that they should shift ground.
Shift ground means, "Leave the place".
"I said I will not leave."
"Well okay, I will leave this place."
Compromise means to overlook certain things to give chance for peace.
Every Monday from now, I want you to be on your knees in your home
and begin to pray for the whole world.